<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kydan&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kydan&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.138.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 15:56:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is DEI part (2 of 8)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025.04.13.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 15:56:47 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025.04.13.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-have-many-large-companies-been-pulling-out-of-dei&#34;&gt;Why have many large companies been pulling out of DEI?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might have heard recently that many large scale companies have been pulling out of DEI such as Target, Meta, Amazon, McDonald&amp;rsquo;s, Pepsi, Google, Walmart and more. Many people seem to not understand why companies are pulling out of their DEI initiatives. There are multiple reasons why companies are withdrawing from DEI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1--economic-considerations&#34;&gt;1.  Economic Considerations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In times of finacial uncertainty, with inflation and recessions, companies might prioritize cost cutting. To many companies, DEI may be seen as non essential so these DEI programs may be the first to face budget reductions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is DEI part (1 of 8)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025.04.13.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 21:23:46 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025.04.13.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a special DEI blog series where I will explore what DEI is and providing unbaised information regarding many topics of DEI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-is-dei&#34;&gt;What is DEI?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DEI is ancronym. It stands for Diversity, Equity and Inclusion. Diversity menas to have varity. In this case however, it could mean having diffrent people, races, genders, ages, religions, abilites or backrounds. Equity means to be fair or equitable. Equity does not mean treating everyone the same way but it means providing the same opertunites for people. It means to recognize that some people might face more obstacles than others and adjusting policers to support to help level the playing field. Inclusion in DEI means to make sure that people feel like they belong. Like they feel equaly valued.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
